# Priyanka Dave

647-835-5565 • Toronto, ON L6A ON8 • priyankasharma080396@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Experienced IT Analyst with 2+ years of experience in troubleshooting, resolving and documenting software and hardware issues. Possess exemplary skills in written and verbal communications. Exposure to maintaining log collection, configuration management and network monitoring systems.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Network Configuration: Switch/Router configuration, Network Security, Firewalls, VPN
- Domain Services: ADDS, Azure Active Directory, Virtualization
- Programming and Automation: Python, Java, PowerShell, Docker
- Database: MySQL, SQL Server, Microsoft Access, SQLite, MongoDB
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux, MacOS
- Ticket Management and Documentation: Salesforce, JIRA, Knowledge Base
- Other skills: Software/Hardware Troubleshooting, Phone & Email Technical Support

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Customer Service Representative—Paymentus, Richmond Hill, Canada

August 2021 – Present

- Processing payments for the client's mutual customers (Inbound and Outbound).
- Assisting customers by explaining procedures, answering questions, and providing relative information in a professional business manner.
- Following call center scripts and processes when handling different topics.
- Working collaboratively with Customer Service, Operations, Marketing, and Sales to improve client satisfaction.

**Software Specialist–** eClinicalWorks, Ahmedabad, India

November 2019 – July 2020

- Provided daily support to users of the system including answering questions, analyzing problems, and quickly forming solutions to return systems to proper operation
- Communicated clearly and effectively with end users, colleagues, and management to quickly resolve issues and ensure customer satisfaction
- Installed and maintained hardware, software, and other equipment to meet client requirements, routinely observed operational performance, and installed security patches and updates when necessary
- Maintained detailed records of daily interactions with customers, installation activities, reported issues, and completed solutions along with any further actions required of management or repair personnel.
- Collaborated with technical staff and clients to establish goals and objectives for system improvements and upgrades.

 Created and implemented new processes to improve efficiency and customer satisfaction while reducing costs.

IT Support Technician— RadixWeb, Ahmedabad, India

January 2019 – November 2019

- Installing, configuring, upgrading and maintaining computer systems and network infrastructure
- Monitoring and maintaining overall health of the system
- Maintaining the inventory and documenting troubleshooting procedures

# **EDUCATION**

Master of Computer Applications – GTU, IndiaAugust 2016 – April 2019Bachelor of Computer Applications – Gujarat University, IndiaAugust 2013 – July 2016

## **PROJECTS**

**Todo app** – Maintain Daily Tasks, August 2022 To-Do List project using HTML, CSS, NodeJs, ExpressJS

- Add a new task in the ToDo List App that needs to be done in a descriptive way.
- View all the ToDos that were added to the list.
- Add as many tasks as you have.
- Modify or Delete any task from the list of ToDos.
- Uses the express framework.

Portfolio Website – Personal Project, July 2022

Responsive Portfolio Website – HTML, CSS, Javascript

- Responsive one page portfolio website Using HTML CSS & JavaScript
- Contains many features like pseudo elements, hamburger, Off-canvas and CSS animations.
- Developed first with the Mobile First methodology, then for desktop.
- Compatible with all mobile devices and with a beautiful and pleasant user interface.

**FaceRec** – L.D. College of Engineering, January 2018 - May 2018 Real-time face recognition using Eigenfaces and Fisherfaces - C++, OpenCV

• C++ based real time system which uses different feature based methods (Eigenface and Fisherface) which identifies and recognize a human face on the level of confidence based upon the training given.

**Library Management System –** L.D. College of Engineering, July 2017 – December 2017 C++

 Can perform book-related operations like a real library management system which can manage books and students details and search books according to Book name and Author. It also performs automatic fine calculation for late returns.

**Try Before You Buy** – Gujarat University, January 2016 - May 2016 Online Shopping Application - Android, PHP

- An Android based application which enables the customers to try clothes virtually before they shop online.
- Customers can try various dresses of various sizes which is available in stock and they can easily choose the best one for them.